import React from "react";


export const QuizData = [

        {
            id : 1,
            question : "Number of Primitive Datatypes in java are ?",
            option : ["6","7","8","9"],
            answer : 3,
        },
        {
            id : 2,
            question : "What is the size of float and double in java?",
            option : ["32 and 64","32 and 32","64 and 64","64 and 32"],
            answer : 1,

        },
        {
            id : 3,
            question : "automatic conversion is possible in which of the possible case ?",
            option : ["Byte to int","int to long","long to int","short to int"],
            answer : 2,
        },
        {
            id : 4,
            question : "When an array is passed to a method, what does the method receive?",
            option : ["The reference of the array","A copy of the array","length of the array","copy of first element"],
            answer : 1,
        },
        {
            id:5,
            question : "When is the object created with new keyword?",
            option : ["At run time","At compile time","Depends on the code","none"],
            answer : 1,
        },
        {
            id:6,
            question : "In which of the following is toString() method defined ?",
            option : ["Java.lang.obj","Java.lang.string","java.lang.util","none"],
            answer : 1,

        },
        {
            id:7,
            question : "compareTo() returns",
            option : ["True","False","An int value","none"],
            answer : 3,

        },
        {
            id:8,
            question : "To which of the following does the class string belong to.",
            option : ["Java.lang","Java.awt","java.applet","java.string"],
            answer : 1,

        },
        {
            id:9,
            question : "Total constructor string class have?",
            option : ["3","7","13","20"],
            answer : 3,

        },
        {
            id:10,
            question : "Output of Math.floor(3.6)?",
            option : ["3","3.0","4","4.0"],
            answer : 2,

        }
];